Hello everyone, this is Mizuki Yamashita. Today I'd like to cook for the first time in a while.
And today I'm not alone. My friends are my friends.
We have a delightful guest with us today.
I misspelled it.
I'm sorry for calling you so early in the morning.
No, no, no, no. Thank you so much for coming.
It's my first time here.
I'm sorry I didn't call you that.
I just thought it'd be more exciting to make something for someone else.
You're so thin.
You're so thin, so I'd like to take you out for dinner sometimes, but I'd like you to eat delicious meals with me.
I'm glad.
Mizuki-san asked me what I wanted to eat with my home-cooked food.
What? What? What? I'm shaking.
I was shaking and trying to do my best, and he said, "Eggs.
Since you like eggs, I'd like to make something for Kakki to eat.
I've made the towel dish before, but I was wondering if you'd like to make another one for Mommy? No, I'm not sure about the soup.
I've never made it before.
Is that so?
I'm sorry if I messed up.
I've never made a mistake.
That's all I'm doing.
I'll make something crazy and you eat it.
I'll eat it.
I'll fill you up.
I feel a little sick. It made me a little sick.
It's kind of old-fashioned and cute.
Then let's make it!
Next time preview
I'm so excited.
What are you going to make today?
Today
Oyako-don
and
Osuimono
Oshi-don
Osuimono ni
Ebi shinjo no osuimono
Oh, my gosh!
You're just stunned.
I don't know what a shrimp shinjo is
Oh, wow!
Surprisingly, Kakki, when we go out to eat, there are so many things I've never had before.
There are a lot of them.
I'm glad you're happy.
Seeing Kakki's face for the first time.
Today is another first for me.
I'm going to make his first shrimp shinjo.
Yay, I remember it every time I see my first shrimp shinjo! Yay, I remember every time I see my first Ebishinjo.
It's true, it's true, it's true.
But it's my first time making ebishinjo, too.
Oh, I see. That's why I'm a little nervous, but I'll do my best.
Well, first of all, before I start cooking, I want to make myself look like this.
Oh, there's a refrigerator. A big refrigerator. Let's take a look inside.
Oh! What's that?
I'm not done yet. What's that?
What's this? What is it? Asahi Super Dry.
I thought I'd have one of these to work on my cooking.
Kakki only drinks water or tea.
Here you go, delicious water!
ASMR
Oooooooh...
It's a nice sound.
Well, I'll make a toast.
Yes, well then, here's to today!
I'll have a toast.
Wow!
Looks delicious!
Delicious! This is delicious!
You know, the first sip of beer really tastes good!
Thank you, Mr. Asahi. Thank you for everything!
Wow, it's super beautiful, this
The screen. Hey, you know, today, the apron selection is a bit, what? Yes, that's right. That needs-me style, a little bit like a wife, a nice wife. Cute.
Well then, let's start cooking. First of all, I would like to cook rice first. Then I would like to start cooking. First of all, I would like to start with rice.
Have you always been a good cook? I have been cooking for as long as I can remember.
I have been cooking ever since I can remember.
My parents' mother was a great cook, so I've been cooking ever since I can remember.
Is that right?
Yes, I started by helping my mother,
When I was in elementary school, I bought a lot of recipe books,
The rice was ready.
I left it alone.
Then, I decided to make shiitake mushrooms first, starting with the soup. Shiitake mushrooms are cute.
First of all, I cut off the shiitake mushrooms, leaving the umbrella part. Shiitake mushrooms are cute. I like shiitake mushrooms.
Oh, really? I'm glad. There are a lot of kids who don't like shiitake mushrooms. I like shiitake the best. What?
I don't know, but it fits my image a little. Shiitake mushrooms? Yes, I like shiitake mushrooms.
I mean, aren't there enoki mushrooms, erinoki mushrooms, maitake mushrooms, and so on? It kind of feels like shiitake mushrooms.
This is the first time I've been told that. Really?
I don't know how to say it. This part of the mushroom, how do you call it? This, this part that grows like this.
Thin. Thin part.
I chop that thin part a little bit.
I do the same. You don't really eat it in the first place.
You don't eat it.
I've only eaten it a few times in my life,
I see.
I was able to decompose the mushrooms by the atmosphere.
Decomposed.
It was disassembled.
Next, Kakki's favorite shrimp. Next, Kakki's favorite shrimp.
Shrimps.
I love shrimp.
Shrimp.
Wow.
Wow. Everything is fun, isn't it?
Shrimps are, uh..,
How do you say it, how do you say it? I beat them up.
I think you can do it with frozen shrimps, too.
Yes, well, when you live alone, you have a lot of leftover ingredients,
I think it's good to use frozen foods.
It's good, isn't it? Kakki, you should do your best.
That's right.
The shrimp turned out like this.
They were beaten up in no time at all.
I beat up the shrimp, too.
Transparent, I don't know what it is.
Good impression.
New girl, this yam is indispensable for new girl.
Ahhh.
What's the best thing about being like a kakki-style mother's taste?
Fried eggs.
After all, it's an egg dish.
That's right. Because I love eggs.
Can you cook omelet? Can you cook an omelet?
He can, but he usually tries to do something about it at the end,
But he usually tries to do something about it at the end.
The last roll.
Oh, I see.
He tries his best to make it beautiful.
I want to try Kakki's egg rolls. I'm really curious.
Like this, grated.
Wow, it's firmer.
Firmer. Firmer.
Good impression. Like this, it's so soft and fluffy.
I was able to grate the yams.
It's very sticky. Isn't the consistency amazing?
The ingredients.
I was able to cut it all. It's all done. Let's go this way first.
The staff put the kelp on it for me. Thank you very much. I would like to put this on the fire first.
Just before it boils. Just to the very last minute. Just barely. No boil?
Oh, yes. If it comes to a boil, it's no good. In the meantime, I would like to proceed with the shrimp thingy.
Maybe...
As for the potato starch, you know, the kind that makes the starch sizzle. The kind that makes it squeak? When you press it, it squeezes. Oh, yes, that's right. Like a squeak. The kind that makes a squeak. Yes, that's right. Persimmons are amazing.
No yams are added. Put the egg white. Shrimp. Shrimp, yes.
Are you on the verge of a "ma'am"? This is the front of the Maiden, this is the front of the Maiden. This is a baby daughter. It's a baby. This is the base of the baby.
Mimiki, you're waiting for the mame baby. We will take good care of you from now on. This is Makeno's baby. A newborn baby was born. Congratulations!
It will take some time to come in February, so I'd like to make oyakodon (parent and child bowl) first. Here is the baby. We have such a large amount of meat.
We have such a large amount of meat. I want to cut it into nice pieces. What kind of meat do you like best? I like chicken best.
Then why don't you bring it? The meat is cut. It's done. I'm going to give you a recipe for oyakodon. Then why don't you bring it? The meat has been cut. It's done. This time, I used a recipe for oyakodon by a cookery researcher named Kentetsu Kou.
I was referring to a recipe by a cookery researcher named Kentetsu Kou, and I saw it on YouTube, and it looked really delicious, so I thought I would use his recipe this time.
Next, onions. I think I used half of an onion. Doesn't it hurt your eyes?
Onions don't hurt my eyes at all. I think my eyes are stronger than onions. My eyes are stronger than onions. My eyes are the strongest. You really do have eyes that can beat anything.
What do you mean? Really? I don't know if I have eyes like this. Cut the onion into thin slices.
The three leaves are decorative leafy eggs like this. Three eggs. That's about three for two servings.
I will discard them. They are beautiful eggs. Wait! The kombu has started to boil.
The kombu has come to a boil, so this is what it looks like. When the kombu comes to a boil, it's bonito flakes. Since it is combined dashi, put bonito flakes and kombu here.
Eiyan, eiyan. That's good, that's good, that's good.
Eiyan, eiyan.
Now all you have to do is wait. About 5 or 6 minutes, I think.
Let's crack it open with one hand.
Wow!
One hand.
Wow! That's great! It's broken.
In a normal oyakodon, I usually mix the ingredients together like this,
But with Satoshi Kouken's recipe, only the white meat is cut like this.
Ehhhhh....
This is quite unusual, but only the white meat is cut, and the yolk is not broken yet.
Ehhhh.
That's right.
Then, rub it.
Oh.
Dabada dabada dabada.
Wow.
Wow, that's good. Wow, great. Wow, nice. Wow.
Put it on the fire and let it simmer for a bit.
Yes, sir. Sake there.
Sake. Wada wada wada.
Soy sauce. Soy sauce.
Harmony. Wa.
Wa. Japanese.
The shiitake mushrooms that Kakki here loves, which I just cut up. Shiitake mushrooms.
Yes, I put it in. By adding shiitake mushrooms, the soup stock of mushrooms comes out.
It's covered in dashi. Yes, it's covered in dashi, really.
There is nothing but dashi.
What are you going to do with so much dashi? Wow.
It started boiling like this.
Now, at last, is it coming? Mr. Shinjo's.
Mr. Shinjo, he's a little different. It's Big Boss Shinjo-san.
Here he comes. Here comes the Shinjo time.
BB grows.
Yes, round like this.
Come on, oh!
But I think this is fun. It would be fun to do it with friends or something.
Sure it is.
With your family, too.
Yes, it would.
With your family.
Oh!
Oh! Beautiful! Oh! Beautiful!
Genius!
It's done!
My son was a genius at making pearls.
Well, maybe the best.
I would like to put a snack bowl in between.
Soy sauce.
Add mirin (sweet cooking rice wine). It's called kareta, kareta.
It's what makes the flavor.
While the kamigata is simmering,
I'll take a look at the pearls.
How are the pearls on site?
Yes.
They look good.
I would like to turn them over.
I wonder what will happen when I turn them over.
I wonder what will happen.
Oh, the mixture is getting very hot.
The scene is getting exciting.
It's a battle, isn't it?
Wow, it's hot.
Put the meat here.
Looks delicious.
It looks delicious. It looks delicious already.
It's absolutely delicious.
Put the meat in the return.
Oh no.
In this way, like Kentetsu-san's recipe, by putting the meat in the return first,
It seems to give it a very strong flavor.
The only thing left is to put the flour.
Just add the flour.
Just powder.
That's a unique expression.
It looks good like this, so I would like to finally put the egg in.
You put only the white meat first, right?
Heh.
Alright.
Now we'll put the lid on once.
I see.
About a minute.
Well, the seaweed will be fine.
When the white meat is ready like this,
Then, when the white meat is done like this, put the stems in here.
You don't have to stir too much in a bowl of umeko,
Just like this. Just a little bit.
About a slice.
Just enough to cut.
Just enough to cut. Just enough to cut it off.
I finally put it in.
Wow.
Soy milk.
Beauty is good. Beautiful women win.
It's a kyun.
It's Kyun.
Kyun is in. It's too close. It's too close.
It was filled with love from Kakki.
Heart was stuffed too.
Well then, be a good boy and go to sleep. Sleep tight.
This is just a light meal.
Oyakodon is delicious even if it's half-boiled.
Oh, wow. Like this.
Ready!
Bon appétit!
Yay!
Let's eat!
Let's start with what we're going to eat, shall we?
That's right!
The first beautiful beverage.
Eat first.
Drink it.
I don't know.
Oh, it's delicious. Oh, it's good.
Is it really? It's soaked in vinegar. Seeped? It's soaked.
It's delicious. It's so delicious.
Yes, it's delicious. It tastes like a lot of soup stock.
It's so fluffy.
Wow, great. Bon appétit.
How is it?
Fluffy.
Fluffy?
And inside...
And the broth inside.
It's so delicious.
New order.
This is the new order.
Delicious! The new order!
New order! Delicious!
It's so neat! Shrimp taste good too!
You're going to go for it?
I'll go for it!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
It's good! Good!
You put egg on it.
The yolk looks like an egg. The yolk is like a great egg, and the white is like a soup stock.
The white part is soup stock? Dashi?
There's the return!
Wow! Oh, good! Delicious!
Well, I'll have it again.
Mmm! Yum!
Delicious! It's so comforting.
It tastes so relaxing.
Oh my gosh, the yolk turned out so well.
It's so good!
Delicious! Oh, good! Delicious!
So, how many stars?
How many stars?
Out of 100
1000 points!
I got one more!
I got a little more!
I also enjoyed making it with Kakki.
It was fun to make it with Kakki!
I don't know how to say it, but it sounds weird.
Even though we made it together, we only put leaves on it.
But Shin-chan helped me make it.But Shin-chan formed it, too.
Indeed.
And hearts, too. He put them in.
Yes, filled with Kakki's love
The love of two people.
It's delicious! Thank you.
It was delicious!
We were so happy.
But it's very easy to make for everyone.
Please try making it if you like!
That's all for Eizuki Yamashita and
and Kaoru Kakihara
Eizuki Yamashita and Kaoru Kakihara's fun chat cooking!
Yay!
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!
The end!